告诉我们你所知道的
- We need to know what you know.
那不是我负责的行动 我不知情
- It wasn't my op. I have no intel.
那次行动没得到批准
- It wasn't authorized.
是的
- No.
你为什么叫我来
Why'd you call me here?
杰果米和凯勒失踪了
- Jeremy and Caleb have disappeared.
你能看到
As you can see,
他们把一个重要人物交给了俄国人
they delivered an asset into the hands of the Russians.
中情局雇佣安东尼·格林和他的团队来阻止他们
CIA contracted Anthony Greene and his team to stop them.
看来是伏击
- Reads like an ambush.
是的发生了枪战
- Yeah, there was a shootout.
那人跑掉了
The asset got away.
我们需要知道他们可能知道的一切
We need to know everything that they might have shared.
我父亲和凯勒怎么了?
- What happened to my father and Caleb?
凯勒逃走了
- Caleb, he fled.
他潜伏了起来
He went underground.
我父亲呢
- My father?
格林说你父亲倒下了
- Greene reported that your father went down,
但他还要赶在别人到达之前
but he had to remove any dead and wounded
转移走所有死伤者
before anyone else arrived.
也的户体在哪里
- Where's his body?
我估计他在俄国人那里
- I'm assuming the Russians got him.
也许凯勒回来了 我不知道
Perhaps Caleb came back. I don't know.
我们回去时现场已经干净了
The site was clean once we arrived back.
从昨晚6点起
As of 1800 hours last night,
他们的身份就改变了
their status has been changed internally.
中情局认为他们是叛徒
The CIA has deemed them as traitors,
悬赏捉拿
and they now have a bounty on their head.
他们在这个组织中的职位
Their position with this organization
已经丧失
has been forfeited
任何和他们一起工作的人都要受到质疑
And anyone working with them is now in question.
你在暗示我是叛徒吗
- Are you suggesting that I'm a traitor?
假以时日 我相信你能
- Within time, I'm sure you can
弥补他们造成的损害
repair the damage that's been done by--
女妖 别这么做
Banshee, don't do this.
你不是国家的故人
You're not an enemy of the state.
你也知道凯勒和我父亲
- We both know that Caleb and my father
忠于这个组织
were loyal to this organization.
鉴于目前的情况
- Well, in light of this current situation,
我对此不太确定
I'm not really sure right now.
别这么做
Don't do this!
从名册中去掉我的名字
- Take my name off your books.
我不干了
I'm out.
等我查明真相后
And when I find out what really happened,
我会报复你们当中
I'll return for all of you
听有任由他俩死去的人
that left them out there to fucking die.
5年以后
我控制了摄像头
- I got control of the cameras.
你可以开始了
You're good to go.
不多逗留就像我们计划的那样
In and out, just like we planned.
大堂里会有两个人
There'll be two in the lobby.
-还有其他人吗 -没看到
- Any others? - None visible.
第二个电梯
Second set of elevators.
你的车已经在路上了
And your chariot is on its way.
那些人不可能是联邦探员
- There's no way those guys are Feds.
他显然知道有人悬赏杀他
- Obviously, he knows there's a price on his head.
这个人到底做了什么坏事
- What the hell did this guy do anyway?
我是杀手 不是法官
- I'm the executioner, not the judge.
该死的
- Damn it!
-克罗诺斯 -等一下
- Kronos? - One second.
遇到一点技术故障
I'm having some technical difficulty.
又被他们控制了?
- Are they taking it back?
不不别担心
- No, no, no. Don't worry.
我需要知道 我是不是在走进陷阱
- I need to know. Am I walking into a trap?
不只有这一部电梯有故障 别担心
- No, it's just an elevator. I wouldn't worry.
跟我说说
- Talk to me.
好吧有一个小问题
- All right, there's one small thing.
没有所谓的小问题
- There's no such thing as a small thing.
我看不到这层楼的摄像头
- I couldn't access the camera on this floor.
还有呢
- And?
有人使我失去了对电梯的控制
- Ugh, someone's overriding my control in the elevator.
做点什么
- Do something.
我没办法
- I can't!
哇
- Well, well, well.
你来了
There she is.
女妖
Banshee...
你还用这个代号吗
You still going with that?
安东尼·格林
- Anthony Greene.
盱眼的功夫
It's been a minute.
你就抢了我的猎物
You took my kill.
让我损失了一百万美元
You just cost me a million dollars.
不
- No.
我没让你损失钱 亲爱的
I didn't cost you a penny, sweetheart.
事实上 我会把这笔赏金让给你
In fact, I'm going to give you the credit and the money.
你只需要交出凯勒
And all you have to do is hand over your boy Caleb.
你还在纠结此事
Oh, man, you're still on that?
不会吧
Really?
挺悲哀的
It's kind of sad, don't you think?
不 我不这么认为
- No, uh, I fucking don't.
凡是能有助于我
'Cause every second that I get closer
找到那混蛋的都是值得的
to that piece of shit is a second well spent.
追踪一个人五年时间有点长
- Five years is kind of a long time to track someone,
但你一心报复也能理解
but a revenge killing is a revenge killing, I guess.
嗯
- Uh-huh.
因为他的所作所为我要他的命
For what he did, I'm going to take his life.
嗯
- Hmm.
你也知道他潜伏了起来
We both know he's off the grid.
他销声若迹了
He's a fucking ghost.
是啊 他销声若迹了
- Yeah, he's a fucking ghost.
听以你是追踪他的最佳人选
That's why you're the perfect person to track him down.
不知道的
- If I didn't know any better,
还以为你是胆小鬼
I would think that you're too big of a pussy
不敢跟我单挑呢
to take me on one-on-one.
哦
- Oh.
闭嘴吧
Shut the fuck up.
我不是来胡闹的
I ain't come here to play.
女妖 好好想想
Banshee, do some thinking.
因为毕竟
'Cause end of the day,
你也知道这事会是什么结局
we both know how this shit's going to end.
不是吗
Don't we?
我知道
- I do.
克罗诺斯 开门
Kronos, open the door!
正打开电梯门
- Opening elevator doors.
上啊
- Go!
-克罗诺斯-我在努力
- Kronos! - I'm trying!
打开了
Got it.
对讲机 她正在下去
- Walkie. She's on her way down.
听见了吗她正在下去
Do you hear me? She's on her way down.
走走
Move, move, move.
看来我们拿不到那100万了
- I take it we're not getting that 1 million.
现在还不行
- Not now.
我很需要这笔钱
- I really needed that money.
门就要打开了你准备好了吗
Door's about to open. Are you ready?
快点吧
- Fucking bring it.
多少人?
How many?
两个在大厅 安东尼在下楼
- Two in the lobby. Anthony's on the move.
我在试图阻止他
I'm trying to stop him.
-克罗诺斯现在发动汽车 -好的
- Kronos, start the car now! - Done.
什么
What?
这都是她一个人干的
So one person did all of this to us.
她在和谁说话
Who was she talking to?
她叫他克罗诺斯-查查
- She called him Kronos. - Go on this.
我要知道他是谁在哪里
I wanna know who he is, where he is.
我要抓住他
I want my hands on him.
把这里清理干净
Clean this shite up.
很刺激啊 女妖
- Well, that was fun, Banshee.
我说过多次了
- Dude, I've told you ten million times
别这么称呼我
do not call me that.
你怎么认识安东尼·格林的?
- How do you know Anthony Greene?
他是前特种部队成员他的人生目标
- He's former Special Forces who's made it his goal in life
就是为中情局追捕罪犯
to hunt down people for the CIA.
那么他是组织的人
- So he's part of the Collective
你想让他死?
and you want him dead?
他杀了一个我亲近的人
- He killed someone who's close to me.
既然他是杀手 为什么手底下还有这么多人
- If he's an assassin, why does he have so many guys?
因为他是胆小鬼 他知道我会杀了他
- Because he's a fucking pussy, and he knows I would kill him.
我需要你帮我找个人
I need you to find someone for me.
这正是我的用场
- That's what I'm here for.
找到凯勒·纳瓦岁
- Find Caleb Navvaro.
你说真的吗
- Are you serious?
凯勒·纳瓦罗?这是我们的目标
Caleb Navvaro? That's our target?
是的
- Yes.
我们说的是同一个凯勒·纳瓦罗吗
- We're talking about the same Caleb Navvaro?
训练你并负责秘密行动的那个
The one that trained you and ran black ops?
就是他
- That's the one.
D. 有上于人叫凯勒·纳瓦罗
- D, there's a thousand people named Caleb Navvaro.
既然格林找不到他 我也不可能找到
If Greene couldn't find him, there's no way I will.
他已经潜伏了五年
He's been underground for five years.
而且我们刚损失了一大笔钱
And we just lost out on a whole lot of money.
我们还是继续下一份合同吧
Can we please just move on to the next contract?
我们不会再有对付安东尼的机会
- We will not have another shot at Anthony.
你说真的吗 你可是以一敌百
- Are you serious? It's you versus a small army.
求你了
Please.
我不能再输给他一次
- I'm not letting him win again.
你已经看过了照片 我都说了他死了
- You've seen the photographs. Told you he's dead.
周末前把这笔钱打到我的账户上
Listen, I want our money in my account by the end of the week.
先生
- Sir?
不 和往常一样 是一百万
- No, as usual, it's a million.
好的
Yeah, sure.
很高兴跟你做生意
Yeah, always a pleasure.
-怎么了 -我有了克罗诺斯的线索
What? - I've a lead on Kronos.
-怎么样-是一流的黑客
- And? - Top-rate hacker.
也是女妖的中间人
Acts as a middle man for Banshee.
几年来他一直是她的耳目
Apparently, he's been her eyes and ears for a few years.
他在哪里
- So where is he?
我还不知道
- I don't know yet.
那就找到他在日出之前
- So find him, and before sun up.
好吧 我看看中情局是怎么说的
- All right, let's see what the CIA has to say.
如果他们知道什么他早就死了
- If they knew anything, he'd be dead,
我们也不会有这次谈话了
and we would not be having this conversation.
是关于叛徒的事吗
- Is this about the traitor thing?
是的还有别的原因
- Amongst other things, yes.
这人的悬赏是1 千万
- The price on this guy's head is 10 million.
我知道
- I know.
那你为什么没杀他
- And you didn't kill him. Why?
你不知道
- You don't understand.
格林和凯勒
Greene and Caleb are worth
对我来说远不止值一千万
so much fucking more to me than 10 mil.
好吧
- All right.
那么你比任何人都了解他?
Would you say you knew him better than anyone?
是的
- Yes.
绝对的
Definitely.
也肯定会犯下失误
- He had to slip up at some point,
泄露过对我们有用的信息
shared some kind of info that could help us.
如果你是凯勒 你会去哪里
If you were Caleb, where would you go?
他来自芝加哥 他会回去吗
He's from Chicago. Would he go back?
不不肯定不会
- Nah, nah, nah, nah. No, no, definitely not.
他在那里太引人注目
He'd gain too much attention there.
最喜欢的度假地点 朋友 家人
- Favorite vacation spots, friends, family,
肯定有什么信息
something, let's--let's work with something here.
威尔堡 查查威尔堡
- Wellburg. Check Wellburg.
-威尔堡在哪里? -新泽西
- Where the hell is Wellburg? - Jersey.
有几处房产
- All right, there's a few homes
是五年前购买的
that were purchased five years ago.
也有一些店铺开张
Some businesses opened up too.
Barb's五金店还有一家意大利餐馆
Barb's Hardware. We have an Italian place.
有个酒吧叫老井酒吧
And there's a bar named Old Well Tavern.
就是这个
- That's it, that's it!
老井酒馆就是这个
Old Well Tavern, that's it.
老井酒馆店主叫沃尔特·赫雷罗
- Old Well Tavern, It's owned by Walter Herrero.
赫雷罗先生在大约三年前
Looks like Mr. Herrero bought the house and bar
买下了房子和酒吧
about three years ago.
嗯
- Mm.
潜伏两年之后再改头换面
Lay low for two years, start a new life.
正是他的风格带我去那里
That's fucking him. Take me there.
更新全球定位系统
- Update the GPS.
人家这才叫打棒球
This is what I call a game.
都是些真正会打的
Players who can actually play.
这是重播瑞克
- It's a rerun, Rick.
也很有看头
- Still.
你懂我的意思吧
You know what I'm saying, right?
我们的主力球员伤病不断替补球员都不行
Our team can't stay healthy, and our bullpen sucks.
呃
- Ugh.
这情况一时半会改变不了
I can't see that changing any time soon.
如果我们球队中有这样的好投手
Imagine if we got some decent pitching like those guys.
嗯
- Hmm.
就是个有实力的棒球队了
- We'd be a ball club worth playing against.
啊 再来一杯
Ah! Another shot.
你的家乡是哪支球队来着
What was the, uh, home team where you come from again?
拉雷多队对吗
Laredo, right?
新拉雷多队在河对面
- Nuevo Laredo, across the river.
嗯
- Mm.
你在那里也有酒馆吗
Do you run a tavern there too?
你总是在上午10 点就喝这么多
- You always drink this much at- 00 a.m.?
克罗诺斯?
- Kronos?
我在
- I'm here.
你今天早上好吗
- How are you this morning?
应该比你强 你开了一整夜的车吗
- Probably better than you are. Did you drive all night?
不 我在一个...
- No, I stopped at some dumpy--
一个...
Some dumpy...
天啊 克罗诺斯别这样
Gee, Kronos, come on, man.
好的我在
- All right, I'm here.
我在
I'm here.
我在一个破旅馆停了车
- Anyway, so I stopped at some dumpy place,
洗了个澡睡了一会
and I had a shower and a little bit of sleep.
简直是度假啊
- Little vacation.
闭嘴
- Shut up.
你快到了
- You're almost there.
我知道
- I know.
跟你说一下
There's something I wanna talk to you about.
我跟他有些私人恩忍
This is kind of a personal matter,
听以我要下线了我得单独去找凯勒
so I'm gonna go offline until I sort things out with Caleb.
我没意见 终于能休息一天了
- No complaints with me. I finally get a day off.
好的
- Good to know.
回头见我的朋友
I'll see you on the other side, my friend.
祝你顺利 女妖
- Godspeed, Banshee.
别这么称呼我
- Don't fucking call me that.
嗯
- Mmm!
你这老板太气人知道吗
You're a real asshole, you know that?
我之所以常来你这个店
The only reason I keep coming back here
是因为我老婆更气人而且你开门早
is because my wife's a bitch and you open early.
-至少能把你忽悠来 -是啊
- Well, at least you come back. - Yes.
是啊
- Yes.
抱歉
- Sorry.
不是我的错
No, it was my fault.
应该道歉的是我
I'm the one who should be sorry.
跟你说 你买上酒就走
And between me and you, get your drinks and leave.
这老板脾气古怪
The owner is a real crank.
他一直都是这样
- He's always been that way.
是啊
Yeah.
这里还有其他人吗
- Anybody else here?
上午客人稀少
- Mornings are quiet.
你身后有一个门
There is a latch right behind you.
你知道该做什么
You know what to do.
你也想放下百叶窗?
- I assume you want these down?
好的
- Sure.
凯勒不要
- Caleb, don't.
我必须这么做
- I have to.
你也一样
And you too.
只要慢慢地
Just slowly.
这很好
That's good.
我也很高兴见到你
- It's great to see you too.
是啊
Yeah.
你是怎么找到我的
- How did you find me?
你说过将来你会买下这个店
- You said you were going to buy this place someday.
嗯
- Hmm.
你当时喝醉了 但是...
- You were drunk, but...
语气真诚
- What? - Sincere.
你还记得这事?
- You remember that?
我不是来杀你的
- I'm not here to kill you.
好
- Okay.
我的悬赏是多少
So what is my price anyway?
四五百万?
4 mil, 5 mil?
一千万
- Ten.
感觉很有面子
- Well, that feels pretty good.
如果
- And it's, uh...
如果你不听我的会有人拿到赏金
it's gonna get collected if you don't listen to me.
安东尼·格林正在追杀你
Anthony Greene is gunning for you.
他抢了我的生意然后伏击了我...
He, uh, beat me to a job and ambushed me...
给我100 万让我供出你
and offered me a mil to give you up.
于是你供出了我?
- So you gave me up.
你拿我当什么人了
- Who do you think I am?
我好几年没见你了 所以我拿不准
- I haven't seen you in years, so I don't know.
这是谁的错
- And whose fault is that?
这次我不会让他跑掉了
I am not gonna let him get away this time.
我一个人对付不了他的大批手下
And I can't handle his army alone.
看来我
- It looks like I...
把你训练得很好
I trained you well.
那么
So...
喂 穿西装的不许动
Hey, Suit, don't move!
这个黑发女孩是谁
- Who's the girl with the black hair?
-是我女儿 -什么
- She's my daughter. - Your what?
海莉她不是坏人
- Yeah. Hailey, she's fine.
她是谁
- Who is she?
她是我以前的同事
- Uh, she's an old friend from work.
你是人质吗
- Are you a hostage?
不是不是
- No! No.
别拿枪指看我们的客人 好吗
Just stop pointing your gun at our guest, right?
你满看我的事太多了
- You have a lot of explaining to do.
是啊
- Yeah.
这位是黛利拉
Well, you know, Hailey, this is, uh, Delilah.
这位是海莉
Delilah, Hailey.
把枪给我
Come on, give me that.
你就等着把钱全输掉吧 "狗妈妈93"
- Get ready to lose everything you own, Dogmom93.
- ♪ Don't talk to me ♪
♪ Don't talk to me ♪
- ♪ I have nothing left ♪
该死的
Ah, damn it!
她是高手
She's good.
- ♪ I told you no ♪
♪ Your chance is-- ♪
嗯
Hmm.
有人吗
Hello?
克罗诺斯这里藏着枪吗
- Kronos, are there any guns hidden in here?
如果有的话我们肯定能找到 所以...
We're gonna find them if there are, so...
就省些力气直接告诉我们吧
make things easier for yourself and tell us.
我一直在披萨盒里放一把左轮手枪
- I always keep a revolver in the pizza box.
嗯
- Hmm.
克罗诺斯
- Kronos.
这个破地方
What a shithole.
你是个赌徒?
So you're a gambler, huh?
这可要很多钱
That's expensive.
你赢过钱吗
You ever won?
今天不走运
- Not my lucky day.
呃
- Eh.
也未必
I wouldn't say that.
目前还未比
Yet.
你就是这种生活?
So this is how you live, huh?
电脑和植物
Computers and fucking plants.
植物不会顶嘴
- Plants don't talk back.
克罗诺斯 坐在这里能更放松一些
- Kronos, perhaps over here would be more comfortable.
好
- Okay.
你知道我一直在找谁吧
- So you know the man I've been looking for, don't ya?
不
No.
我有预感
Well, I got a hunch
你知道他在哪里
that you know exactly where the fuck he is.
不
No.
如果你不知道也许女妖知道
Well, if you don't know where he is, maybe Banshee does.
而你肯定知道她在哪里
And I know for sure you know where she is.
我是来跟你谈生意的
I'm here to offer you something.
这里
That there...
是一百万美元
is a million dollars.
你平时的分成是多少
Now, what's your usual cut?
两成?
20% maybe?
看看这人的胆量
Look at the balls on this guy.
告诉他
Tell him.
你的真名是迈克尔·谢伊·汤姆森
- Your real name's Michael Shea Thomson.
毕业于麻省理工学院获得了计算机科学学位
You graduated from MIT with a degree in computer science
然后进了国土安全部
before joining the Department of Homeland Security,
在那里你时时刻刻
where you spent every waking moment
防止俄罗斯的网络攻击
preventing Russian cyberattacks.
后来你发现干私活挣钱更多
That is, until you realized there's more money
就改了行
in contracting and made the switch.
他了解我
- He knows me.
是的我们了解你
- Yeah, we know you.
你父母双亡
Your mom and dad are dead.
我找不到爱你的人
And I can't find anyone who loves you
来要挟你
that I can terrify and hurt.
那么
So...
我是不是应该杀了你自己去找女妖?
do I just kill you and then find Banshee on my own?
不是吗
No?
留着你也好因为我不太懂电脑
Well, that's kinda handy 'cause I'm not much of a computer guy.
可这个房间里的这四个人
But these four people in this room
非常非常擅长伤害别人
are very, very good at hurting people.
他们会折磨你几个小时
And they will hurt you for hours.
我有必要让你活着吗
Now, do I have to keep you alive?
完全没有
Not at all.
留着你有用吗
Is it convenient for me?
也许吧
Maybe.
我想负责你的合同
- I wanna run your contracts.
我想成为你的耳目
I wanna be your eyes and your ears.
我想负责你的电脑
I wanna be your new cyber guy.
我为什么要这么做?
- Why would I do that?
因为我能把女妖给你
- 'Cause I can give you Banshee.
我们做这笔交易
Let's make this deal.
你给我女妖你给我迦勒
- You give me Banshee, you give me Caleb.
但如果你想耍我我会找到你的
But if you try and fuck me, son, I'll find ya.
你妈妈是画家吗
- Is your mom a painter?
生前是
- Was.
她去世了
She's dead.
南希四年前诊断出患有癌症
- Nancy got diagnosed with cancer four years ago.
在我们搬来之前几个月去世了
She--she died a few months before we moved here.
对不起
- I'm sorry.
好
Yeah.
既然她是你的朋友
- If she's your friend,
怎么会不知道妈妈的事
then how does she not know about Mom?
我们的关系并不密切
- Well, we--we--we weren't that close, actually.
你在开玩笑吗
- Are you kidding?
你们在说什么
- What are you guys talking about?
你爸和我爸非常亲密
- Your dad and my dad were very close,
所以我们一起长大
so we grew up together.
你爸也从事建筑业?
- Was your dad in construction?
我们一起从事建筑业
- We worked into-- in construction together.
是的 有一段时间
- Yep, well, there was a time...
我们常有些危险
we'd be in some kind of danger spots and--
是啊 建造高楼的时候
- Yeah, like when we had to build skyscrapers
我们互相照应
and had to have each other's backs.
这跟不认识我妈有啥关系
- What does any of that have to do with not knowing about Mom?
已经是很久以前的事了 海莉 真的
- Well--it's been a long time, Hailey, really.
是的
Yeah.
可她知道我们在哪里
- Well, she knows where we are.
-她知道黑帮的事吗 -海莉 行了
Does she know about the mob? - Hailey, enough.
你作业都做完了吗
Don't you have some homework to do
不去看电视了?
or a show to watch on television?
-好吧 -好
- Fine. - Good.
我上楼去
- I'll go upstairs.
谢谢
- Thank you.
对不起我...好吧
Hey, I'm sorry. I'm--okay. All right.
再见
- Good night.
建筑工人?
Construction worker?
不会吧
Really?
你说啥不好
Out of all the options that you had,
非要说建筑工人?
you went with construction worker?
是的
- Yeah.
大城市的建筑工地
Construction sites in big cities
经常会来些黑社会
can get tangled with dirty people,
我就更有借口搬到小镇了
giving me a reason to move to a small town.
所以就...建筑工
So construction.
哦 那么你在躲着黑社会
- Ah, so you're hiding from the mob?
难怪她上来就掏枪
Makes sense, why she said hello at gunpoint.
哦 你在训练她对抗黑社会
Oh, and you're training her to fight the mob.
跟你当年训练我
Well, it's interesting because it's very similar
很类似
to how you trained me.
是啊
Yeah.
你想谈谈安东尼
So you wanted to talk about Anthony.
-是的 -嗯
- Yes. - Mm-hmm.
那晚他跟你和我父亲在一起吗
- Was he there that night with you and my father?
不 不 别再谈我的过去了
- No, no, no, no. We're done with my past, eh?
我们谈的是安东尼
We're talking about Anthony.
这与你的过去无关
- This isn't about your past.
你是...
You are--
你曾是我的好教官
you were such an amazing mentor for me.
我需要你
And I need you.
真的
I really do.
我需要你帮我
I need your help.
你所有的问题都是关于安东尼
- You know, all your questions are for Anthony.
是的 他当时也在
Yeah, he was there.
他一个人吗
- Was he alone?
他带人来了吗
Did he bring anyone?
这重要吗
- Does it matter?
不
- No.
你要跟这个黑老大干架?
- So you're gonna fight Stalin Jr.?
-不是 -哦
- No. - Oh.
是我们跟他干架
- We are going to fight him together.
难道你想射藏一辈子吗
Don't you wanna stop hiding?
过去是改变不了的
- Can't change the past.
我挺好的
I am fine.
我在这里挺好的
I'm fine right here.
你是怎么了?
- What happened to you?
我...
- You know, I--
我跟你一样
I wish your father was here
都希望你父亲还活着
as much as you do.
我了解孤独的感觉
I know what it feels like to be alone.
做杀手也并非人生的全部
There is more to life than just contract killing.
我现在很满足
I'm happy now.
满足于现状是的
Right here, right now, yes.
我很高兴你能满足
- Well, I'm happy for your happiness.
谢谢
- Thank you.
但是...
But, um...
我不会去当你的诱饵
I am not gonna be your bait.
你这招挺不错
- Hey, it was a good move.
是你教得好
- Well, you taught me well.
等等
Hold on.
你父亲的档案是后面两份
The files on your dad are two in back.
晚安女妖
- Good night, Banshee.
谢谢你
- Thank you.
不客气
- You're welcome.
玛丽亚这位是纳瓦罗先生
- Malia, this is Mr. Navvaro.
他是我和我们组织的朋友
He's a friend of myself and our organization.
呃
- Uh...
玛丽亚小姐我听说你父亲·
Miss Malia, I--I understand, uh, your father is,
是个有权势的人
uh, is a powerful man.
你知道他是什么人
- You know who he is.
是的
- I do.
我想知道你是什么人
I would like to know who you are.
我也想知道
And I also would like to know
这件事对你有什么好处
what do you get out of this whole thing?
保护 我只希望得到保护
- Protection. All I want is protection.
这个当然
- But, yeah.
但我们不会因为
But you don't get protection
你父亲是亿万富翁就保护你
just because your father is a billionaire.
我不能批准
You know I can't grant it.
这硬盘上的内容只是一小部分
- On that drive is just a taste.
客户交易
Customers, transactions,
最重要的是多数国家都没听说过的
but most important, blueprints to weapons
武器的设计图
most governments don't even know about.
那个国家一旦得到他窃取的情报
The government, with all the secrets he's stolen,
能缩短10年的发展时间
takes a leap forward by ten years.
好
- Right.
-都在里面了 -肯定的
- It's all there. - I'm sure it is.
也可能这都是假的
Or it's all fake
你只是给我们下套
and you're just, uh, setting us up.
我不管你们怎么想
- I don't care what you suits think.
我给你他所有买家的名字
I get you the names of all his buyers
以及他所有武器的位置
and the locations of all his weapons,
就给我提供保护
and I get protection.
他是个大恶人
He's a monster,
我需要你们把我藏的离他越远越好
and I need you to hide me as far away from him as you can.
好
- Right.
我会打几个电话
I'll make some calls, yeah.
早上好
Good morning.
嗯
Hmm.
原来是这样
- So that's what happened.
我就知道
I knew it.
我就知道我就知道
I knew it, I knew it, I knew it.
我就知道
I fucking knew it.
我爸爸在哪?
Where's my dad?
向前看你知道什么都没有改变
- Move on. You know nothing has changed.
什么都没
Nothing.
也们没找到他的户体
- They didn't recover his body.
他可能还活着
He could still be out there.
女妖 我看见他倒下了
- Banshee, I saw him go down.
可他们没找到他
- But they didn't find him.
他可能还活着
He could still be out there.
我昨天跟你说过 这...
- You know, I-I-I told you yesterday, that's, uh--
这问题要问安东尼
- That's a question for Anthony.
早上好
- Good morning.
我打扰你们了吗
- Am I interrupting something?
没有
- Uh, no.
我们只是在喝咖啡
Just, uh, having a cup of coffee.
说到这个我该走了
Speaking of which, uh, I should be going.
呃
Ugh.
D. 有事就向酒馆打电话
D, call the tavern if anything comes up.
这酒馆有一个前门还有个后门
- The pub has a front and a back door
通向一个停车场
that leads to a parking lot.
布局很简单
It's pretty straightforward.
凯勒的事可没什么是简单的
- There's nothing straightforward about Caleb.
那房子呢
What about the house?
是在被树林包围的死胡可
- Dead-end streets surrounded by woods.
女妖可能在那里
- Banshee's probably there.
这意味着凯勒知道你们要来
That means Caleb knows that you're coming.
我们要去
- We're coming?
你不去吗
Are you not going?
我的天
- Oh, Jesus Christ, you know what?
你想再质疑我一次吗
You want to question me again?
来啊
Please.
非要我再换一个助手吗
Do I need to find another assistant?
还要多久
How long?
六个小时左右
- Um, six hours or so.
打电话给费城的人
Call the Philly team.
怎么安排
- What are you thinking?
兵分两路
- Two teams.
一路负责房子一路负责酒馆
One takes the house, one takes the tavern.
他们一小时内就能到
They can be there within the hour.
告诉去老井酒馆的人
And tell the team that goes to the Old Well,
要仔细要安静
you know, be subtle, be quiet.
凯勒很精明有可能是白跑一趟
Caleb is smart. It may all be for not.
让他们到了之后就通知我
Tell them to text me when they're in position.
是
- Got it.
提醒他们我要活的
- And remind them I want him alive.
活蹦乱跳的要交给我处置他
Alive and kicking 'cause he's mine.
-知道了吗 -知道了
You got it? - Got it.
那就打电话吧
- So make the damn call.
你给我买个外卖我饿了
You, find me a take-away. I'm starving.
好 我们15点出发
- All right, so we head out at 1500.
不能早也不能晚
No sooner, no later.
务必要避开大路
Stay off the main road at all cost.
不能有任何不速之客
We wouldn't want any uninvited guest during the party.
我们到达市郊后就上土路
Now, when we reach the outskirts of town, we hit dirt.
直到我们看到一个废弃的包装厂
Now, all off-road until we find an old packing house
在大约7公里外
about seven clicks out.
在那里移交给中央情报局
There, the handoff to the CIA happens.
男性和女性特工
Male and female agents,
他也们会带走玛丽亚和她的硬盘进行保护性拘留
they will take Malia and her drives into protective custody.
好吗都满意吗
Good? Happiness?
好了去喝点咖啡打个盹准备一下
All right, so get some coffee, take a nap, and be ready.
-杰里米 等等 -怎么了
- Jeremy, wait. - What is it?
这计划看起来不错纳瓦罗先生
- This all sounds great, Mr. Navvaro.
但是呢
- But?
但是没有B计划
- But there's no Plan B.
这是一次常规行动
- This is a routine op.
我们已经做过上百次了
We have done it hundreds of times,
我的人靠得住相信我
and I trust my men, believe me.
你采取了很多措施
- Seems as though you've taken every precaution
来防范我父亲的人
against my father's men,
他们现在肯定在外面找我
who are definitely out there hunting for me right now.
但你没有对你自己的人采取防范措施
But you've taken no precautions against your own men.
玛丽亚恕我直言
- Malia, if I may,
事到临头 你出现紧张
it is normal to be a little nervous
甚至多疑都是很正常的
or even paranoid as we get closer to the handoff.
但是...
- Is it.. - But--
多疑总比粗心强吧
- More rational to be paranoid or careless?
我冒重大风险来这里
I am risking everything being here.
你不知道如果他抓到我会对我做什么
You have no idea what he'll do to me if he catches me.
我已经履行了我的承诺
I've held up my end of the bargain,
你们也要履行承诺
and I expect you to do the same.
我们是的
- We are.
你们见过接手我的特工了吗
Have you met the agents I'm being handed off to?
当然
- Of course.
他们是中情局特工有最高权限
They are CIA agents with top clearance.
中情局一直是最值得信赖的组织
- The CIA's always been the most trustworthy organization.
放心交给我们吧玛丽亚
- Let us do our job, Malia.
六个月后你可以住在任何你想住的地方
In six months, you will be living wherever you want
做任何你想做的事
and doing whatever the fuck you want.
相信我好吗
Trust me, okay?
好
Okay.
喂 没事的
- Hey, it's okay.
以前是我的最爱之一
- Used to be one of my favorites.
现在不是了?
- Used to?
结局并不美好的话 回忆也就不再美好了
- Memories suck when you know how they end.
你是咋回事
So what's your deal?
我咋了
- My deal?
你来请我爸帮忙
- You came here to get my dad's help,
可你啥都没带
but you haven't done anything
除了吃就是看我家人的照片
but eat and stare at photos of my family.
你们是旧情人吗
Were you lovers or something?
不是
No.
我七岁时就认识他了
I've known him since I was seven.
他有危险吗
- Is he in danger?
我知道他和黑社会有过节
Look, I know he's in danger with the mob.
我看了桌上你的档案
I looked at your file on the table.
你是政府的人吗
Are you with the government or something?
你不该看的
- You shouldn't have done that.
对不起我没办法
- I'm sorry. I couldn't help it.
我觉得他有危险 他是我唯一的亲人
I feel like he's in danger, and he is all I have left.
喂 如果他有危险我需要知道
Hey, if he's in danger, I need to know,
我不能让他...
because I will not let anything--
别说了
- Stop!
我是来帮你们的
I'm here to help you.
现在告诉我你知道的一切
Now, tell me everything that you know.
坐下
Sit.
粗旷但又安静的酒吧老板
- Tough, but quiet bar owner.
我喜欢
Love it.
先来三瓶啤酒吧
Let's start with, uh, three beers.
好的
- Sure.
好
All right.
要几张菜单
- And some menus.
抱歉厨师病了
- Oh, I'm sorry, but, uh, the cook is sick.
那没关系
- That's fine then.
实际上我们在庆祝
We're celebrating, actually.
好啊
- All right.
是的 我儿子要结婚了
- Yep, my son's getting married.
哦哇
- Oh, wow.
没有比威尔堡更适合办婚礼的地方了
Well, nothing says wedding destination like Wellburg.
啊
- Ah!
-他在这里长大 -是啊
- He grew up here. - Yeah.
在他迈出人生重要一步前
- It's like one last bit of nostalgia
带他来这里怀旧一下
before he takes that next big step in life.
感觉你儿子没你开心啊
- Hey, you know, you seem happier about it than he is.
这没办法
- Ah, what can I say?
看来他知道自己要走进围城了
Guess he knows what he's getting himself into.
说的也是
- Yeah, it's true.
失陪一下诸位
Excuse me, gentlemen.
-他们到了 -很好
- They're in position. - Good.
让他们动手
Give them the go.
让另一路人去那栋房子
And tell the other team to hit the house.
找到他们掌握的我的任何把柄
And make sure they find anything they may have on me,
抓活的 等我去那里
and to keep him alive until I get there.
我没看多少
- I didn't read much of it.
我只看了尸体的照片
I just saw pictures of bodies
和类似核密码的术语
and buzz words like nuclear codes.
会有人来这里吗
Are people coming here?
是的
- Yes.
我们该怎么办?
- What are we gonna do?
是我爸爸
It's my dad.
嗨 老婆
- Hey, Baby.
我忘了告诉你
You see, I forgot to tell you
修理工要去一趟
that the repairman is coming by.
他们来了
- They're here.
好我会尽快回去
- Yeah, I'll be there as soon as I can, yeah.
好 替我亲一下宝宝
Uh, yeah, give a kiss to the baby for me.
-我会的 -谢谢再见
- I will. - Thank you. Bye.
拿起你的枪
- Get your gun.
快
Now!
说实话
- Honestly...
我见过更厉害的
I have seen worse.
你的演技确实很高
I mean, you were very good, very good.
但这两个
But these two?
演的就一塌糊涂了
They preform like wet towels.
三个入口还有吗
- Three entrances. Any others?
走廊尽头是地下室入口
- Basement entrance comes out down the hall.
海莉 我要你上楼去
- Hailey, I want you to go upstairs,
把自己锁在房间里
lock yourself in your room.
我说安全之前不要出来
And do not come out until I say it's clear.
我不会扔下你不管
- I'm not leaving you alone.
海莉 走
- Hailey, go!
放开我
- Let me go!
走 开起来
- Get off! Get up!
你放心
- Don't worry.
你死后我会照顾你女儿
I'll take care of your girl when you're gone.
嗨
- Hey.
孩子
Baby.
Hey, baby.
喂
Um...hey...
她需要知道真相..
she needs to know the truth...
别对她说谎
before she hears lies.
是的
- Yes.
很抱歉我之前没有告诉你
- I'm so sorry I didn't tell you this before.
对不起
I'm sorry.
没关系
- It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
是吗
- Hmm, yeah?
以前是我训练你
I, you know, I have trained you.
现在你要听D. 的了好吗
And you have to listen to-- to D now, all right?
知道吗
You understand me?
知道了
- I understand.
-你知道.. -很好 很好
- You understand what I'm trying--good, good.
把她藏起来
Hide her.
我会的
- I will.
你知道他们想要她吧?
- You know they want her, right?
是的
- Yes.
孩子 你...
- Hey, Baby, you're...
你是我一生中的最爱
you're the best thing that ever happened to me.
去房子里的那一路人有消息吗
- What's the word on the team that had the house?
没消息
- Not a thing.
好吧他们都死了
- Okay, they're dead.
也许他们只是在等着...
- I mean, maybe they're just waiting--
不会他们死了
- Nah, they're dead.
监视者呢
What about the spotters?
他们已经就位了
- They're in position now.
凯勒的车在那单但没看到他或女妖
Caleb's car's there, but no sign of him or Banshee.
那么 他们躲在房子里等着我们
- So they're holed up in the house waiting for us.
你听到了什么
What're you hearing?
我们三个人都死在酒馆里了
- Our three are dead inside the tavern.
会追查到我们头上吗
- And is there anything to link them back to us?
警方认为是一起抢劫案
- Cops think it was a robbery gone wrong.
他们正在找酒馆老板
They're trying to find the owner.
后援多久才能来
- How long before we get some backup?
又有一批人正从市里前来
- There's another team coming from the city now.
他们三小时后会到
They'll be here in three hours.
让他们快点
- Ugh, make sure they hustle.
我需要这些混蛋
I want these assholes.
-万一他们跑了呢 -能跑哪里
- What if they run? - Where?
出城只有一条路
There's only one way out of town.
监视者会看到他们的
The spotters will see them.
所以现在我们只是等着
So now, we just sit back and we play the waiting game.
他想让我知道什么?
- What was it he wanted me to know?
他的真实身份
- The truth about who he was.
中情局派了一个叫安东尼的人去杀他们
The CIA sent a man named Anthony to kill them.
说他们是叛徒
They said that they were traitors
把证人的情报卖给俄罗斯人
selling witnesses' intel to the Russians.
中情局为什么要这么做
- Why would the CIA do that?
他们变老了
- They were getting old.
能力太强知道的也太多
They were too powerful, and they knew too much.
操
- Fuck!
凯勒藏了起来
- Caleb went into hiding.
我父亲被枪杀了
My father had been shot.
安东尼的弟弟也被杀了
And Anthony's brother had been killed.
安东尼会来这里吗
- So Anthony will come here?
我希望如此
- I fucking hope so.
很好
- Good.
你有计划吗
Do you have a plan?
我正在研究
- I'm working on one.
跟我来
- Come with me.
这会有帮助吗
Will this help?
这些他都留着
- He kept all these?
他只信赖它们
- He had trust issues.
我真幸运
Lucky me.
我们应该去楼上 这对我们有利
We should take the upstairs. It'll be to our advantage.
我爸说停在一个地方是送死
- My dad said if you aren't mobile, you're dead.
正常情况下是这样
- Normally, that's true.
但我们去哪里都会被他们找到
But if we go anywhere, they'll find us.
这房子是我们的主场
This house is our territory.
对我们最有利
It's advantageous to us.
-他们不会烧房子吗 -不可能
- Won't they just burn us out? - No way.
他们需要凯勒的尸体作为杀人证据
They need Caleb's body as proof of kill.
我的头上也有赏金
I have a price on my head,
他们也想领赏
so they'll wanna collect that too.
你带了多少人
- How many you got?
足够多
- Enough.
让他们进去
- Send them in.
他到底是什么样的人?
- What was he really like?
什么
- What?
我爸爸他到底是什么样的人
- My dad. What was he really like?
我想你可能最了解他
- I think you probably knew him best.
了解另一个版本的他
You just knew a different version of him.
你了解哪个版本?
- Which version did you know?
我了解那个高大强壮的硬汉凯勒
I knew the big, strong, I'm-a-bad-ass Caleb.
他外表强悍但是
He had a hard shell, but...
他对有的人也很心软
he had a soft spot for a few people.
你失去父母的时候是什么感觉
- What was it like when you lost your parents?
很痛苦
- It was hard.
心里有怒火
I was angry.
但我只是低着头专注于工作
But I just kept my head down, focused on the work,
专注于目标
and eye on the prize.
那么他真的没提过我们
- So he really never mentioned us?
没有
- No.
这说明他爱你们胜过一切
Which means he loved you more than anything.
也在保护你的安全
He was protecting your safety
即使对他身边的人也不提及
even from the ones that he trusted the most.
那么现在只有我们了?
- So you guess it's just us now?
是的
- Yes.
没关系
- That's fine.
我挺喜欢你的
Kinda like you.
我也挺喜欢你
- Kinda like you too.
他们为什么不下车?
- Why are they not getting out?
过来
- Come here.
你在做什么
- What are you doing?
他们在使用热成像 我们需要伪装成一个人
- They're using thermal. We need to register as one.
看来前门被封住了
- Looks like the front door is boarded up.
对讲机
- Walkie.
绕到后面去
Go around the back.
看看是不是也一样
Make sure it's the same.
是
- Roger that.
院子对面有两个人
- Two guys across the yard.
后门也被封上了
- Back door's boarded up too.
他们把房子封起来就走了吗
- Did they just board it up and leave?
我只看到一张热成像图
- All I'm seeing is one thermal image,
所以你在胡说什么
so what the fuck are you talking about?
楼下有人吗
- Is there any sign of life downstairs?
没有 我绕到后面去
- Negative. I'll go around back.
先生 如果这是个陷阱呢
- Sir, what if it's a trap?
肯定是陷阱
- Of course it's a trap.
但我需要知道第二个人是谁
But I need to know who the second person is.
在凯勒出来前用这个找到答案
Use this to find out before Caleb's on.
是时候了
It's time.
喂 女妖
- Hey, Banshee!
小贱人 小贱人
Little bitch! Little bitch!
该玩玩了
Time to play!
来吧 女妖
Come on, Banshee.
我知道你在里面
I know you're in there.
D. 别管我
- D, don't worry about me!
杀了这个混蛋
Kill this bastard!
女妖
- Banshee...
你真的要让你的人死吗
are you really going to let your boy die?
做点什么
- Do something.
我不能
- I can't.
安东尼是唯一知道我父亲下落的人
Anthony's the only one who knows about my father.
哦
- Oh!
后面再去三个人
Three more in the back.
走
Go.
三个人绕到后面去了他们来了
- Three going around back! They're coming in!
哦 该死的
- Oh, fucking Christ!
冲进房子 冲进房子
Rush the house! Rush the house!
情况如何
- How's it going?
不妙
- Not great!
真没用
Fucking useless.
一直被他们踢开
They keep kicking them before they go off!
-煮一下 -什么
- Cook 'em. - What?
煮一下手雷
- Cook 'the grenades.
我听不懂
- I don't know what that means!
在手里擦一下再扔出去
- Hold them for a few seconds before you throw them.
一 二 三
- One, two, three...
你有枪吗
- You got a gun?
你现在有了
You do now.
走吧
Come on.
五六个人来了
- Five or six coming in!
-看到安东尼了吗 -我不知道
- Eyes on Anthony? - I don't know!
他们都戴着面具
They're all wearing masks!
这混蛋想拖垮我们
- Fucker's trying to wear us down.
现在上楼去
Go upstairs now.
操
Fuck!
走 走
- Go. Go, go, go, go!
总算来了
- Finally.
滚
- Fuck off.
你的人还有活着的吗
Do you got any men left alive?
不知道我想他们都死了
- I don't know. I think they're all dead.
不 我做不了
- No, I can't do this.
你当然可以
- Of course you can.
听我说
Listen to me.
要活捉房里的人
Who we find in that building, I want them alive.
你是认真的吗
- Are you serious?
是的 我是认真的
- Yeah, I'm serious.
在我把他们装进裹户袋之前 我是很认真的
Until I put them in body bags, I'm very serious.
走
Go.
操
Fuck.
喂
- Whoa!
哇
Wow.
看看你女孩
Look at you, girl.
干得好
Good job.
凯勒在哪?
Where's Caleb?
去啊
Go, go, go!
凯勒在哪?
Where's Caleb?
我有个主意
- I have an idea.
你让你的人放过她
How about you get your fucking dudes off the girl?
我告诉你凯勒在哪 你告诉我我父亲在哪
I'll tell you where Caleb is, you tell me where my father is,
人人都满意
everybody's fucking happy.
我不记得你父亲在哪里
- I don't recall where your father is.
你撒谎
- You're a liar.
你说得对
You know what? You're right.
我记得
I do recall.
我最后一次见到他时
The last time I seen him,
有几个人把他揍得屁滚尿流
there was a couple of guys beating the shit out of him.
他躺在血泊中
And he was lying in a pool of blood.
我真傻
Silly me.
快进来
- Get the fuck in here!
对一个十几岁的女孩来说有点过分了
- Feels like a little much for a teenage girl!
他们没找到尸体
- They never found a body.
可能因为你父亲是个叛徒 他跑了
- Or because your father's a traitor, and he ran away.
错 让他们放过那女孩
- Wrong. Get them off the fucking girl!
凯勒在哪?
- Where's Caleb?
埋在后院
- Buried in the back yard.
现在你让我生气了 因为我知道你在撒谎
- Now you're upsetting me because I know you're lying!
在凯勒杀了我的人之后
'Cause after Caleb shot my men,
我知道他回到了这里
I know he came back here.
他在哪里
Where the fuck is he?
哦 你想打?
- Oh, you're feeling tough?
好吧
Okay.
我们按传统方式来
Let's do this old school.
开枪啊
- Shoot her!
Shoot her!
喂 喂
- Yeah. Hey, hey, hey.
凯勒
Where...
在
the fuck...
哪里?
is...Caleb?
啊?
Huh?
你出拳绵软无力
- You punch like a little fucking bitch.
喂 混蛋
- Hey, asshole.
去死吧
Fuck you.
操
- Fuck.
还有吗
- Are there more?
但愿没了
- I hope not.
我今天中了枪
- I got shot today.
我也杀了人
- I got shot too.
不 我中了枪
- No. I got shot.
在肩膀上
In the shoulder.
是皮肉伤 你没事的
- It's a flesh wound. You'll be okay.
下一步是什么
- What's next?
还会有人对我们开枪吗
Are more people gonna shoot at us?
大概吧
- Probably.
这取决于我们去哪里 要去杀谁
It just depends on where we go and who we go after.
但现在 我们去个旅馆房间
But for now, let's just get a cocktail
喝杯鸡尾酒吃些牛排
and a steak in a hotel room.
这是我最想做的
- There's nothing I'd rather do.
♪ I have no home ♪
♪ I have nowhere to be ♪
♪ I'm a wanderer ♪
♪ That's me ♪
♪ And I don't care how you judge me ♪
♪ I don't care what you think of me ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ There is darkness ♪
♪ And the rain is pouring down ♪
♪ There is violence all around ♪
♪ And I don't need you to hold me ♪
♪ I don't need you to take care of me ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ So what do you want? ♪
♪ What do you want from me now? ♪
♪ You can't hurt me, no ♪
♪ And you can't help me out ♪
♪ And I will scream like a banshee ♪
♪ I will scream like a banshee ♪
♪ So what do you want? ♪
♪ What do you want from me now? ♪
♪ You can't change me, no ♪
♪ And you can't chain me down ♪
♪ I will scream like a banshee ♪
♪ I will fight, you can't block me ♪
♪ I have no fear, you won't stop me ♪
♪ I will win, you can't beat me ♪